Finding Aid for Provost and Executive Vice-President for Academic Affairs (University of Michigan) Central Files
Bentley Historical Library
- Central Files
  - 1975-1976
    - Alphabetical Files
      - Kraus Memorial Lecture (Box 73)
      - L-General (Box 73)
      - Lansing: Miscellaneous State Offices, 2 folders (Box 73)
      - Legislative Bills (Box 73)
      - Libraries (Box 73)
      - Long-Range Planning Committee (Box 73)
      - M-General (Box 73)
      - Malpractice Insurance (Box 73)
      - Mellon Foundation: Values in a Secular Society (Box 73)
      - Mental Health Research Institute (Box 73)
      - Michigan Council for the Humanities (Box 73)
      - Michigan Council of State College Presidents (Box 73)
      - Michigan Historical Collections, Bentley Historical Library (Box 73)
      - Michigan State University (Box 73)
      - Michigan Student Assembly (formerly Student Government Council) (Box 73)
      - Middle English Dictionary (Box 73)
      - Minority Affairs, 2 folders (Box 73)
      - Museum of Art (Box 73)
      - N-General (Box 73)
      - Named Professorships (Box 73)
      - National Humanities Center (proposed) (Box 74)
      - National Science Foundation (Box 74)
      - Nordby, Virginia B. (Policy Coordinator, Academic Affairs) (Box 74)
      - North Central Association (Box 74)
      - Norton (W. W.) and Company (Box 74)
      - O-General (Box 74)
      - Overberger, Charles G. (Vice President for Research)
        - General (Box 74)
        - DNA Research (Box 74)
      - P-General (Box 74)
      - Payroll Procedures (Box 74)
      - Periodic Health Appraisal Unit (PHAU) (Box 74)
      - Personnel Availability Assessment (Box 74)
      - Personnel Office, 2 folders (Box 74)
      - Ph.D. Enrollment (Box 74)
      - Ph.D. Enrollment: Replies to Memo (Box 74)
      - Physical Education Program (Box 74)
      - Pierpont, Wilbur K. (Vice President and Chief Financial Officer) (Box 74)
      - Plant Extension Committee (Box 74)
      - Policies and Procedures (Box 74)
      - Policy Coordinator Position (Box 74)
      - Population Studies Center (Box 74)
      - Power Exchange Scholarship (Box 74)
      - President's Club (Box 74)
      - Professional Theatre Program (Box 74)
      - Program Evaluation: Responses to Phase I Questionnaire (Box 74)
      - Program Evaluation Committee (Box 74)
      - Q-General (Box 75)
      - R-General (Box 75)
      - Radock, Michael (Vice President for University Relations) (Box 75)
      - Regents' Correspondence (Box 75)
      - Registration and Records, Office of (Box 75)
      - Reserve Officers Training Corps (ROTC) (Box 75)
      - S-General (Box 75)
      - Saginaw Valley College (Box 75)
      - Salary Information (Administrative) (Box 75)
      - Sarkar, S. S. (letter of recommendation) (Box 75)
      - Saudi Arabia (Box 75)
      - Sauve, Robert P. (Assistant to VPAA) (Box 75)
      - Scheduling Office (Box 75)
      - Scholarships (Box 75)
      - Senate, University
        - Senate Advisory Committee on University Affairs (SACUA): Non-Tenured Appointments (Box 75)
        - Senate Advisory Review Committee: Virginia Nordby Position Paper (Box 75)
      - Siena Heights College (Box 75)
      - Space (Box 75)
      - Staff Benefits (Box 75)
      - State Department of Education (Box 75)
      - Student Appeal Procedures (Box 75)
      - Student Government Council (Box 75)
        (see also "Michigan Student Assembly")
      - Student Loans (Box 75)
      - Students (Box 75)
      - Supplemental Retirement Income (for Retired Personnel) (Box 75)
      - Swets, Paul (letter of recommendation) (Box 75)
      - T-General (Box 75)
      - Technical Bargaining (Box 75)
      - Television Center (Box 75)
      - Term III (Box 75)
      - Texas at Austin, University of (Box 75)
      - Title IX: Discrimination (Box 75)
      - Tropical Studies, Organization for (OTS) (Box 75)
      - Union Negotiating Team (Box 75)
      - University Consortium Center (Box 75)
      - University Council (Box 75)
      - University Press (Box 75)
      - University Value Years (Box 75)
      - V-General (Box 75)
      - W-General (Box 75)
      - Women (Box 75)
        (see also "Institute for Academic Advancement of Women")
      - Wright, Robert P. (letter of recommendation) (Box 75)
      - X-Y-Z-General (Box 75)
      - Index to Correspondence, 1975-1976 (Box 75)
    - Schools and Colleges Files
      - Architecture and Urban Planning, College of (Box 76)
      - Art, School of (Box 76)
      - Business Administration (Box 76)
      - Dearborn Campus (Box 76)
      - Dentistry, School of (Box 76)
      - Education, School of
        - General (Box 76)
        - Complaints and Grievances (student) (Box 297)
      - Engineering, College of (Box 76)
      - Extension-Dearborn and Flint (Box 76)
      - Flint Campus (Box 76)
      - Graduate School
        - General, 2 folders (Box 76)
        - Reports, 2 folders (Box 76)
      - Law School (Box 76)
      - Library Science, School of (Box 76)
      - Literature, Science and the Arts, College of
        - General, 2 folders (Box 77)
        - Miscellaneous Areas, Departments, Centers (Box 77)
        - Astronomy
          - General (Box 77)
          - Grievances (Box 297)
        - Biological Sciences Group (Box 77)
        - Chemistry (Box 77)
        - Computer and Communication Sciences (Box 77)
        - Counseling Office (Box 77)
        - Economics (Box 77)
        - English (Box 77)
        - Far Eastern Languages & Literature (Box 77)
        - Geography (Box 77)
        - Geology & Mineralogy (Box 77)
        - Germanic Languages and Literature (Box 77)
        - History (Box 77)
        - History of Art (Box 77)
        - Journalism (Box 77)
        - Linguistics (Box 77)
        - Mathematics (Box 77)
        - Museum of Paleontology (Box 77)
        - Museum of Zoology (Box 77)
        - Near Eastern Studies (Box 77)
        - Philosophy (Box 77)
        - Physics (Box 77)
        - Political Science (Box 77)
        - Psychology (Box 77)
        - Romance Languages (Box 77)
        - Slavic Languages (Box 77)
        - Sociology (Box 77)
        - Speech (Box 77)
      - Medical School
        - General, 4 folders (Box 78)
        - Medical School Review (Box 78)
        - Medical Campus Library and Learning Resource Center (Box 78)
        - Medical Service Plan (includes Executive Board), 2 folders (Box 78)
        - Report of Joint Medical School, Hospital Task Force to Review Emergency Medical Services, October 31, 1975 (Box 78)
      - Music, School of (Box 78)
      - Natural Resources, School of (Box 78)
      - Nursing, School of (Box 78)
      - Pharmacy, College of (Box 78)
      - Public Health, School of (Box 78)
      - Social Work, School of (Box 78)
  - 1976-1977
    - Alphabetical Files
      - Academic Affairs Advisory Council, 2 folders (Box 79)
      - Academic Affairs Planning and Analysis, Office of, 2 folders (Box 79)
      - Academic Planning: Phase II (Box 79)
      - Academic Services Board (Box 79)
      - Admissions Office (Box 79)
      - Affirmative Action
        - General (Box 79)
        - Commission on Minorities and Women (Box 79)
        - Committee (Box 79)
      - Allied Health (Box 79)
      - Allmand, Charles M. (Assistant to VPAA) (Box 79)
      - Alumni Association (Box 79)
      - American Association of University Professors (AAUP) (Box 79)
      - American Council on Education (ACE) Academic Internship (Box 79)
      - Appointments (Box 79)
      - Ashby, Lord (Box 79)
      - Association of American Universities (AAU) (Box 79)
      - Athletics (Box 79)
      - Audits, Internal (Box 79)
      - Awards
        - Amoco Good Teaching (Box 79)
        - Faculty Achievement (Box 79)
        - Faculty Service (Box 79)
        - Graduate Teaching Assistants (Box 79)
        - University (Box 79)
      - B-General (Box 79)
      - Barbour-Waterman Gym, 3 folders (Box 80)
      - Brinkerhoff, James, Vice President-Elect (Box 80)
      - Budget
        - General, 3 folders (Box 80)
        - Formula Funding (Box 80)
        - Program Closures, 2 folders (Box 80)
        - 1977-1978 (Box 80)
      - Bylaws (Box 80)
      - C-General (Box 80)
      - Carroll, Philip S (Box 80)
      - Center for Continuing Education of Women (Box 80)
      - Center for Higher Education (Box 80)
      - Center for Human Growth and Development (CHGD) (Box 80)
      - Center for Research on Economic Development (CRED) (Box 80)
      - Center for Research on Learning and Teaching (CRLT) (Box 80)
      - Centers: General (Box 80)
      - Committees: General (Box 80)
      - Complaints (Box 80)
      - Computer and Communication Sciences (Box 80)
      - Computer Policy Committee (Box 80)
      - Computing Center (Box 80)
      - CRISP (Computer Registration Involving Student Participation) (Box 80)
      - D-General (Box 80)
      - Daane, Ketelhut, Lemmer (General Counsel) (Box 80)
      - Data Systems (Box 80)
      - E-General (Box 80)
      - East Asian Studies (Box 80)
      - Ethics and Religion (Box 80)
      - F-General (Box 80)
      - Faculty Bargaining (Box 80)
      - Faculty Development Funds, 2 folders (Box 81)
      - Family Practice Residency Planning Committee, May 1976 (Box 81)
      - Fees, Student (Box 81)
      - Financial Aid Office (Box 81)
      - Ford, Gerald R., President and Mrs. (Box 81)
      - Freedom of Information Act (Michigan), Ad Hoc Committee (Box 81)
      - G-General (Box 81)
      - General Counsel (Box 81)
        (see "Daane,...")
      - Graduate Employees Organization (GEO), Affirmative Action (Box 81)
      - H-General (Box 81)
      - Health and Human Values, Task Force on, Report, September 1975 (Box 81)
      - Health, Education, and Welfare, Department of (Box 81)
      - Health Maintenance Organization (Box 81)
      - Health Sciences, Division of, Committee (Box 81)
      - Health Service (Box 81)
      - Honorary Degree Committee (Box 81)
      - Hospital, University
        - General, 3 folders (Box 81)
        - Mission and Role, February 1977 (Box 81)
        - Planning (Box 81)
        - Planning Committee (Box 81)
      - House Officers' Organization (Residents and Interns) (Box 81)
      - Housing Office (Box 81)
      - Housing Project, New Single Students (Box 81)
      - I-General (Box 82)
      - Indirect Cost Reimbursement (Box 82)
      - Institute for Human Adjustment (Box 82)
      - Institute for Public Policy Studies (IPPS) (Box 82)
      - Institute for Social Research (ISR) (Box 82)
      - Institute for the Study of Mental Retardation and Related Disabilities (ISMRRD) (Box 82)
      - Institute of Gerontology (IOG) (Box 82)
      - Institute of Labor and Industrial Relations (ILIR), 2 folders (Box 82)
      - Institute of Science and Technology (IST) (Box 82)
      - Institutes: General (Box 82)
      - International Programs and Center (Box 82)
      - J-General (Box 82)
      - Johnson, Henry (Vice President for Student Services) (Box 82)
      - K-General (Box 82)
      - Kennedy, Richard L. (Vice President for State Relations) (Box 82)
      - L-General (Box 82)
      - Lansing, Offices in, 3 folders (Box 82)
      - Libraries (Box 82)
      - M-General (Box 82)
      - Malpractice Insurance (Box 82)
      - Memberships (Box 82)
      - Mental Health Research Institute (MHRI) (Box 82)
      - Michigan Council of State College Presidents, 2 folders (Box 82)
      - Michigan Historical Collections, Bentley Historical Library (Box 82)
      - Michigan Society of Fellows (Box 82)
      - Michigan Student Assembly (formerly Student Government Council) (Box 83)
      - Michigan Theatre Association (Box 83)
      - Minority Students (Box 83)
      - Museum of Art (Box 83)
      - N-General (Box 83)
      - National Endowment for the Humanities (NEH) (Box 83)
      - National Institute of Occupational Safety and Health Research Facility (NIOSH) (Box 83)
      - North Central Association (Box 83)
      - O-General (Box 83)
      - Open Meetings Bill (Box 83)
      - Overberger, C. G. (Vice President for Research) (Box 83)
      - P-General (Box 83)
      - Periodic Health Appraisal Unit (PHAU) (Box 83)
      - Personnel (Box 83)
      - Plant Extension (Box 83)
      - Policies and Procedures (Box 83)
      - Policy Coordinator (Virginia B. Nordby) (Box 83)
      - Population Studies Center (Box 83)
      - Program Closure (April 1977) (Box 83)
      - Program Evaluation Committee (Box 83)
      - Promotions (Box 83)
      - R-General (Box 83)
      - Regents' Correspondence (Box 83)
      - Registration and Records (Box 83)
      - Retirement, Early (Box 83)
      - Russell (Joseph and Marion) Professorship (Box 84)
      - S-General (Box 84)
      - Salary Information (Box 84)
      - Scheduling Office (Box 84)
      - Scholarships (Box 84)
      - Senate, University
        - Assembly (Box 84)
        - Senate Advisory Committee on University Affairs (SACUA) (Box 84)
      - Space (Box 84)
      - State Department of Education (Box 84)
      - Students (Box 84)
      - T-General (Box 84)
      - Tenure (Box 84)
      - Title IX: Discrimination (Box 84)
      - Tropical Studies, Organization for (OTS) (Box 84)
      - Turner, Scott (bequest) (Box 84)
      - U-General (Box 84)
      - Unions (Box 84)
      - University Press (Box 84)
      - University Value Years (Box 84)
      - W-General (Box 84)
      - X-Y-Z-General (Box 84)
    - Schools and Colleges Files
      - Architecture and Urban Planning, College of (Box 84)
      - Art, School of (Box 84)
      - Business Administration, School of (Box 84)
      - Dearborn (Box 84)
      - Dentistry, School of
        - General (Box 84)
        - Complaints and Grievances (faculty/staff), 2 folders (Box 297)
      - Education, School of
        - General (Box 85)
        - Complaints and Grievances (faculty/staff) (Box 297)
        - Physical Education (Box 85)
        - Review Committee, Spurr External Review (Box 85)
      - Engineering, College of (Box 85)
      - Extension: Dearborn and Flint (Box 85)
      - Flint (Box 85)
      - Graduate Studies, Rackham School of (Box 85)
      - Law School (Box 85)
      - Library Science, School of (Box 85)
      - Literature, Science and the Arts, College of
        - General, 2 folders (Box 85)
        - Anthropology (Box 85)
        - Astronomy (Box 85)
        - Biological Sciences (Box 85)
        - Chemistry (Box 85)
        - Classical Studies (Box 85)
        - Complaints and Grievances (faculty/staff), 2 folders (Box 297)
        - Complaints and Grievances (students) (Box 297)
          [Student records restricted until July 1, 2062 ]
        - Economics (Box 85)
        - English (Box 85)
        - Far Eastern Languages (Box 85)
        - Geography (Box 85)
        - Geology and Mineralogy (Box 85)
        - History (Box 85)
        - Journalism (Box 85)
        - Kelsey Museum of Archaeology (Box 85)
        - Mathematics (Box 86)
        - Miscellaneous Areas, Departments, and Centers (Box 86)
        - Museum of Zoology (Box 86)
        - Near Eastern Studies (Box 86)
        - Philosophy (Box 86)
        - Physics (Box 86)
        - Political Science (Box 86)
        - Psychology (Box 86)
        - Residential College (Box 86)
        - Romance Languages (Box 86)
        - Speech (Box 86)
      - Medical School
        - General, 4 folders (Box 86)
        - Medical Service Plan (Box 86)
        - Speech and Audiology: Closure, 2 folders (Box 86)
      - Medical/Osteopathic Schools in Michigan, Costs and Output Study, May 1976 (Box 87)
      - Music, School of, 2 folders (Box 87)
      - Natural Resources, School of (Box 87)
      - Nursing, School of, 2 folders (Box 87)
      - Pharmacy, College of (Box 87)
      - Public Health, School of
        - General (Box 87)
        - Population Planning, Department of, 3 folders (Box 87)
      - Radiology, Department of (Box 87)
      - Social Work, School of (Box 87)
      - Speech and Hearing (Box 87)
  - 1977-1978
    - Alphabetical Files
      - A-General (Box 88)
      - Academic Affairs Advisory Committee (Box 88)
      - Academic Affairs Advisory Council
        - Minutes and Agendas, 3 folders (Box 88)
        - Sussman (Alfred) Files (Box 88)
      - Academic Affairs Planning and Analysis (Box 88)
      - Academic Affairs Staff (Box 88)
      - Academic Planning: Phase II (Box 88)
      - Academic Services Board (Box 88)
      - Administrative Systems, Supervisory (Box 88)
      - Admissions Office (Box 88)
      - Affirmative Action Advisory Committee, 2 folders (Box 88)
      - Affirmative Action Office (Box 88)
      - Affirmative Action Operations Committee (Box 88)
      - Allied Health (Box 88)
      - Allmand, Charles M. (Assistant to VPAA) (Box 88)
      - Alumni Association (Box 88)
      - American Association of University Professors (AAUP) (Box 88)
      - American Council on Education (ACE)
        - General (Box 88)
        - Internship Program (Box 88)
      - Appointments (Box 88)
      - Appointments and Leaves (Box 88)
      - Association of American Universities (Box 88)
      - Athletes (Box 88)
      - Audits, Internal (Box 88)
      - Awards (Box 89)
        - General (Box 89)
        - Teaching Assistants (Box 89)
      - B-General (Box 89)
      - Brinkerhoff, James F., Vice President and Chief Financial Officer (Box 89)
      - Budget
        - General, 2 folders (Box 89)
        - Budget Priorities Committee (Box 89)
        - Capital Outlay (Box 89)
        - Hearings in Lansing
          - October 28, 1977 (Box 89)
          - November 14, 1977 (Box 89)
          - February 23, 1978 (Box 89)
        - Budget, 1978-1979
          - General (Box 89)
          - Projected Budget (Box 89)
          - Request (Box 89)
      - C-General (Box 89)
      - Calendar, University (Box 89)
      - Capital Campaign (Box 89)
      - Career Planning and Placement Office (Box 89)
      - Center for the Continuing Education of Women (Box 89)
      - Center for Higher Education (Box 89)
      - Center for Human Growth and Development (CHGD) (Box 89)
      - Center for Research on Learning and Teaching (CRLT) (Box 89)
      - Centers: General (Box 89)
      - City/University Consortium (Box 90)
      - Commencement (Box 90)
      - Committees
        - General (Box 90)
        - Administration-Instruction Budgets, Committee on Trends in (Box 90)
        - Computer Policy Committee (Box 90)
        - Conflict of Interest Committee (Box 90)
        - Economic Status of the Faculty, Committee on (CESF) (Box 90)
        - Institutional Cooperation, Committee on (CIC), 3 folders (Box 90)
        - Inteflex Policy Committee (Box 90)
        - Research and Transportation, Committee on, 2 folders (Box 90)
      - Complaints (Box 90)
      - Computing Center
        - General (Box 90)
        - Director Search (Box 297)
      - Conflict of Interest (Box 90)
      - Course Evaluation (Box 90)
      - D-General (Box 90)
      - Daane, Ketelhut, Lemmer (General Counsel) (Box 90)
      - Data Systems Center (Box 90)
      - Davis, Carolyne K. (Associate Vice President for Academic Affairs)
        - General (Box 90)
        - Unit Meetings re: Budget (Box 90)
      - Deans and Directors, Memos to (Box 90)
      - Deans, Directors, and Department Heads, Memos to (Box 90)
      - Deans, Meetings with (Box 90)
      - Development Office (Box 90)
      - Distinguished University Professorships (Box 90)
      - Division of Research Development and Administration (DRDA) (Box 90)
      - Dougherty, Edward A. (Assistant to VPAA) (Box 90)
      - E-General (Box 90)
      - Economics (Box 91)
      - English, Richard A. (Associate Vice President for Academic Affairs)
        - General (Box 91)
        - Units Budget Meeting (Box 91)
      - Enrollment (Box 91)
      - Enrollment, Racial and Ethnic Groups (Box 91)
      - Environmental Research Council (Box 91)
      - Ethics and Religion (Box 91)
      - Extension Service (Box 91)
      - External Degrees (Box 91)
      - F-General (Box 91)
      - Faculty
        - General (Box 91)
        - Collective Bargaining (Box 91)
        - Development (Box 91)
      - Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act of (FERPA), 1974 (Box 91)
      - Fees
        - Graduate Student, Report (Box 91)
        - Student, 2 folders (Box 91)
      - Financial Aid Office, 2 folders (Box 91)
      - Fleming, Robben W., President (Box 91)
      - Ford Foundation (Box 91)
      - Ford, Gerald R (Box 91)
      - Freeze (on positions) (Box 91)
      - G-General (Box 91)
      - General Counsel (Box 91)
      - Graduate Employees Organization (GEO)
        - General, 3 folders (Box 91)
        - Appeal (Box 91)
      - H-General (Box 92)
      - Handicapped (Box 92)
      - Health, Education and Welfare, Department of
        - General, 2 folders (Box 92)
        - Audit Report, 2 folders (Box 92)
      - Health Maintenance Organization (HMO) (Box 92)
      - Health Service (Box 92)
      - Hold Credits (Box 92)
      - Hospital, University, 3 folders (Box 92)
      - House Officers Organization (Interns' Union) (Box 92)
      - Housing Office (Box 92)
      - Indirect Cost Reimbursement (Box 92)
      - Inquiries, 2 folders (Box 92)
      - Institute for Human Adjustment (Box 92)
      - Institute for Social Research (ISR) (Box 92)
      - Institute of Gerontology (IOG) (Box 92)
      - Institute of Labor and Industrial Relations (ILIR) (Box 92)
      - Institute of Public Policy Studies (IPPS) (Box 93)
      - Institute of Science and Technology (IST) (Box 93)
      - Institutes: General (Box 93)
      - International Programs and Center (Box 93)
      - Johnson, Henry (Vice President for Student Affairs)
        - General (Box 93)
        - Budget Meeting, March 29 (Box 93)
      - K-General (Box 93)
      - Kennedy, Richard L. (Vice President for State Relations) (Box 93)
      - L-General (Box 93)
      - Lansing Offices (Box 93)
      - Library, University
        - General (Box 93)
        - Budget Meeting, February 23, 1978 (Box 93)
      - M-General (Box 93)
      - Memberships (Box 93)
      - Michigan Council of State College Presidents, 2 folders (Box 93)
      - Michigan Historical Collections, Bentley Historical Library (Box 93)
      - Michigan Student Assembly (Box 93)
      - Michigan Union (Box 93)
      - Minority Enrollment Report (Box 93)
      - Minority Students (Box 93)
      - Miscellaneous Appointments (Box 93)
      - Museum of Art (Box 93)
      - N-General (Box 93)
      - North Central Association (Box 93)
      - O-General (Box 93)
      - Overberger, C. G. (Vice President for Research)
        - General, 3 folders (Box 93)
        - Meeting, April 17, 1978 (Box 93)
      - P-General (Box 94)
      - Periodic Health Appraisal Unit (PHAU) (Box 94)
      - Personnel, 3 folders (Box 94)
      - Plant Extension (Box 94)
      - Policies and Procedures (Box 94)
      - Policy Coordinator (Virginia B. Nordby) (Box 94)
      - Population Studies Center (Box 94)
      - Power Exchange Scholarships (Box 94)
      - President's Club (Box 94)
      - President's Report (Box 94)
      - Priority Funding Budget, 1977-1978 (Box 94)
      - Privacy, Rights of (report) (Box 94)
      - Professional Theatre Program (PTP) (Box 94)
      - Program Discontinuance (Box 94)
      - Program Evaluation Committee (Box 94)
      - Project Advance (English Credit) (Box 94)
      - Promotions (Box 94)
      - R-General (Box 94)
      - Radock, Michael (Vice President for University Relations)
        - General (Box 94)
        - Budget Meeting, March 29, 1978 (Box 94)
      - Recommendations (H.T. Shapiro) (Box 94)
      - Regents' Correspondence (Box 94)
      - Registration and Records, Office of (Box 94)
      - Research Club (Box 94)
      - Research-News, Reporter, and Council (Box 94)
      - Research Seminar in Quantitative Economics (Box 94)